Guide to the Comic book collection, about 1984-2004.
Comic book collection
- X-Factor (v.1), 1992; 84 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: Larry Stroman
- X-Factor (v.1), 1993; 87 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1993; 88 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1993; 89 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1993; 90 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1993; 91 (Box 31)
- X-Force (v.1), 1991; 1 (Box 31)
- X-Force (v.1), 1993; 16 (Box 31)
- X-Force (v.1), 1993; 17 (Box 31)
- X-Force (v.1), 1993; 17 (Box 31)
  Notes: Bagged with card
- X-Force (v.1), 1993; 18 (Box 31)
- X-Force (v.1), 1993; 21 (Box 31)
- X-Force (v.1), 1993; 22 (Box 31)
- X-Force (v.1), 1993; 23 (Box 31)
- X-Force (v.1), 1994; 117 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 1 (Box 31)
  Notes: One copy with wrap-around cover; 1 copy with Beast cover
- X-Men, 1991; 2 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 3 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 4 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 5 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 6 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 8 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 9 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 10 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 11 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 14 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 15 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1991; 19 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1993; 20 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1993; 21 (Box 31)
- X-Men, 1993; 157 (Box 31)
- X-Men & Clandestine, 1996; 1 (Box 32)
- X-Men & Clandestine, 1996; 2 (Box 32)
- X-Men and Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 1 (Box 32)
  Author: Paul Smith
  Artist/Penciler: Bob Wiacek
- X-Men and Alpha Flight (v.1), 1986; 2 (Box 32)
- X-Men and the Micronauts, 1983; 1 (Box 32)
- X-Men and the Micronauts, 1983; 2 (Box 32)
- X-Men and the Micronauts, 1983; 3 (Box 32)
- X-Men and the Micronauts, 1983; 4 (Box 32)
- X-Men Archives Featuring Captain Britain, 1996; 4 (Box 32)
- X-Men Archives Featuring Captain Britain, 1996; 5 (Box 32)
- X-Men Archives Featuring Captain Britain, 1996; 7 (Box 32)
- X-Men Classics, 1983; 1 (Box 32)
- X-Men Classics, 1983; 2 (Box 32)
- X-Men Classics, 1983; 3 (Box 32)
- X-Men Unlimited, 1993; 1 (Box 32)
- X-Men Unlimited, 1993; 43 (Box 32)
- X-Men: Alpha, 1994 (Box 32)
  Artist/Penciler: Roger Cruz
  Notes: Age of Apocalypse crossover
- X-Men: Omega, 1994 (Box 32)
- Xombi, 1994; 0 (Box 32)
- Xombi, 1994; 1 (Box 32)
- Xombi, 1994; 2 (Box 32)
- Xombi, 1995; 11 (Box 32)
  Artist/Penciler: J.J. Birch
- X-Patrol, 1996; 1 (Box 32)
  Author: Karl & Barbara Kesel
- X-Terminators, 1988; 1 (Box 32)
- X-Terminators, 1988; 2 (Box 32)
- X-Terminators, 1988; 3 (Box 32)
- X-Terminators, 1988; 4 (Box 32)
- Young Heroes in Love, 1997; 1 (Box 32)
  Author: Dan Rasper
  Artist/Penciler: Dev Madan
- Young Heroes in Love, 1997; 2 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1998; 1 (Box 32)
  Artist/Penciler: Todd Nauck
- Young Justice, 1998; 2 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1998; 3 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1999; 4 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1999; 5 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1999; 6 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1999; 7 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1999; 8 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1999; 9 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1999; 10 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1999; 11 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1999; 12 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1999; 13 (Box 32)
- Young Justice, 1998; 1000000 (Box 32)
  Notes: Part DC One Million crossover event; published between #2 and #3
- Young Justice 80-Page Giant, 1999; 1 (Box 32)
- Young Justice Special: No Man's Land, 1999; 1 (Box 32)
  Author: Chuck Dixon & Scott Beatty
  Artist/Penciler: Andy Kuhn
- Young Justice: the secret (girlfrenzy), 1998; 1 (Box 32)
- Young Men, 25 (Box 32)
- Zatanna, 1993; 1 (Box 32)
  Artist/Penciler: Esteban Maroto
- Zatanna, 1993; 2 (Box 32)
- Zatanna: Everyday Magic, 2003 (Box 32)
  Artist/Penciler: Rick Mays
- Zero Hour, 1994; 0 (Box 32)
  Notes: Crossover event; published in reverse numerical order starting with 4
- Zero Hour, 1994; 1 (Box 32)
- Zero Hour, 1994; 2 (Box 32)
- Zero Hour, 1994; 3 (Box 32)
- Zero Hour, 1994; 4 (Box 32)
- Zombie World: Champion of the Worms, 1997; 1 (Box 32)
  Artist/Penciler: Pat McEown
- Zombie World: Champion of the Worms, 1997; 2 (Box 32)
- Zombie World: Champion of the Worms, 1997; 3 (Box 32)
- Zombie World: Home for the Holidays, 1997 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1984; 5 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1984; 6 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1984; 7 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1984; 8 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1984; 9 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 10 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 10.5 (Box 32)
  Publisher: Not Available Comics
  Notes: Bagged with issue 13
- Zot!, 1985; 11 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 12 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 13 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 14 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 14.5 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 15 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 16 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 17 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 18 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 19 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 20 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 21 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1985; 22 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 23 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 24 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 25 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 26 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 27 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 28 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 29 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 30 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 31 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 32 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 33 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1986; 34 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1987; 35 (Box 32)
- Zot!, 1987; 36 (Box 32)